let reasoningquestions = {
    time: 30, // in minutes
    questions: [
        {
            question: "1. If all roses are flowers and all flowers are plants, then which of the following is true?",
            option1: "All roses are plants",
            option2: "All flowers are roses",
            option3: "All plants are flowers",
            option4: "None of the above",
            correctresponse: "All roses are plants",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "2. If the first two statements are true, is the final statement true? 'All cats are animals. All animals are mammals.' 'All cats are mammals.'",
            option1: "True",
            option2: "False",
            option3: "Not Determinable",
            option4: "None of the above",
            correctresponse: "True",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "3. Which number comes next in the series: 1, 4, 9, 16, 25, ___?",
            option1: "30",
            option2: "36",
            option3: "40",
            option4: "50",
            correctresponse: "36",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "4. If two pencils cost 30 cents, how much would five pencils cost?",
            option1: "50 cents",
            option2: "60 cents",
            option3: "75 cents",
            option4: "1 Dollar",
            correctresponse: "75 cents",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "5. What is the next number in the sequence: 3, 6, 12, 24, 48, ___?",
            option1: "50",
            option2: "96",
            option3: "60",
            option4: "72",
            correctresponse: "96",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "6. If all squares are rectangles and all rectangles are parallelograms, which of the following is true?",
            option1: "All squares are parallelograms",
            option2: "All rectangles are squares",
            option3: "All parallelograms are rectangles",
            option4: "None of the above",
            correctresponse: "All squares are parallelograms",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "7. Which of the following is the odd one out?",
            option1: "Apple",
            option2: "Banana",
            option3: "Grape",
            option4: "Carrot",
            correctresponse: "Carrot",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "8. If 5 workers can build a wall in 10 days, how many days will it take for 10 workers to build the same wall?",
            option1: "5 days",
            option2: "10 days",
            option3: "20 days",
            option4: "15 days",
            correctresponse: "5 days",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "9. Which of the following is the odd one out?",
            option1: "Football",
            option2: "Basketball",
            option3: "Cricket",
            option4: "Tennis",
            correctresponse: "Cricket",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "10. In a family of 6 members P, Q, R, S, T, and U, T is the father of Q. R is the son of S. P is the sister of S. U is the mother of R. How is S related to Q?",
            option1: "Father",
            option2: "Mother",
            option3: "Brother",
            option4: "Sister",
            correctresponse: "Mother",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "11. What is the missing number in the series: 2, 5, 10, 17, 26, ___?",
            option1: "37",
            option2: "34",
            option3: "39",
            option4: "40",
            correctresponse: "37",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "12. Which of the following is the odd one out?",
            option1: "Square",
            option2: "Rectangle",
            option3: "Triangle",
            option4: "Circle",
            correctresponse: "Circle",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "13. What comes next in the sequence: 1, 4, 9, 16, ___?",
            option1: "20",
            option2: "25",
            option3: "24",
            option4: "22",
            correctresponse: "25",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "14. Which of the following is the odd one out?",
            option1: "Dog",
            option2: "Cat",
            option3: "Horse",
            option4: "Fish",
            correctresponse: "Fish",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "15. If two trains are moving towards each other at the same speed, how long will it take for them to collide if they are initially 200 miles apart?",
            option1: "100 hours",
            option2: "50 hours",
            option3: "10 hours",
            option4: "5 hours",
            correctresponse: "10 hours",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "16. Which of the following does not belong to the group?",
            option1: "Lion",
            option2: "Tiger",
            option3: "Cat",
            option4: "Elephant",
            correctresponse: "Elephant",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "17. What is the next number in the series: 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, ___?",
            option1: "13",
            option2: "10",
            option3: "11",
            option4: "15",
            correctresponse: "13",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "18. In a row of children, A is 6th from the left and B is 7th from the right. If the total number of children is 15, what is the position of B from the left?",
            option1: "9th",
            option2: "8th",
            option3: "10th",
            option4: "11th",
            correctresponse: "9th",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "19. Which number will complete the series: 3, 6, 9, 15, 24, ___?",
            option1: "32",
            option2: "30",
            option3: "28",
            option4: "36",
            correctresponse: "36",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "20. In a certain code language, 'GADGET' is written as 'HBEUHF'. How would 'MOBILE' be written in the same code?",
            option1: "NPEMHF",
            option2: "LNPJFD",
            option3: "NPJMGF",
            option4: "NQJMHG",
            correctresponse: "NPEMHF",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "21. If some students are teachers and all teachers are students, which of the following is true?",
            option1: "Some students are not teachers",
            option2: "All teachers are students",
            option3: "All students are teachers",
            option4: "None of the above",
            correctresponse: "All teachers are students",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "22. Which is the next number in the sequence: 1, 4, 9, 16, 25, ___?",
            option1: "36",
            option2: "45",
            option3: "55",
            option4: "60",
            correctresponse: "36",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "23. How many months have 28 days?",
            option1: "1",
            option2: "2",
            option3: "12",
            option4: "None",
            correctresponse: "12",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "24. If five cats can catch five mice in five minutes, how many cats are needed to catch 100 mice in 100 minutes?",
            option1: "5",
            option2: "100",
            option3: "50",
            option4: "None of the above",
            correctresponse: "5",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "25. What is the odd one out?",
            option1: "Banana",
            option2: "Apple",
            option3: "Grapes",
            option4: "Potato",
            correctresponse: "Potato",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "26. What is the next number in the series: 0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, ___?",
            option1: "13",
            option2: "12",
            option3: "11",
            option4: "10",
            correctresponse: "13",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "27. How many sides does a hexagon have?",
            option1: "4",
            option2: "6",
            option3: "8",
            option4: "5",
            correctresponse: "6",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "28. What will come next in the sequence: 10, 20, 40, 80, ___?",
            option1: "150",
            option2: "100",
            option3: "160",
            option4: "120",
            correctresponse: "160",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "29. In a family, A is the son of B. C is the father of D, and D is the brother of A. How is B related to C?",
            option1: "Father",
            option2: "Uncle",
            option3: "Brother-in-law",
            option4: "Father-in-law",
            correctresponse: "Brother-in-law",
            time: 1,
        },
        {
            question: "30. If a person walks 5 km towards the north, then turns left and walks 3 km, then turns left again and walks 5 km, how far is he from the starting point?",
            option1: "0 km",
            option2: "3 km",
            option3: "5 km",
            option4: "8 km",
            correctresponse: "3 km",
            time: 1,
        }
    ]
};

export default reasoningquestions;
